<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your Future</title>
    <link>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Your Future</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>true</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/about2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/about2/</guid>
      <description>This James Madison High School Project was sponsored by Bryan Johnson. He is an entrepreneur and investor, the founder of Kernel, OS Fund, and Braintree. You can read about him on his website: bryanjohnson.co.
Sky Zoom and Amartya Banerjee, two Madison High School juniors, led the project’s implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>No, there is not a word count. Write enough so that you can explain your idea fully, but not so that it’s a full on dissertation. Be imaginative, and write about what you are passionate about, not necessarily what you think others may be. No rubric will be used, but responses will be judged based on originality and creativity—your imagination of novel perspectives and your passion for effecting positive change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Process</title>
      <link>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/process/</guid>
      <description>Answers to this question will be reviewed by a panel of JMHS faculty judges on Jan. 23 (last day for submission), and the 10 selected finalists’ papers will be sent to Bryan Johnson in Los Angeles for winner selections. The three winners will be announced on Feb. 2nd at MADTalks, where Johnson will speak. Each winner will receive $500 in seed funding from Bryan Johnson.
Email your project in PDF format to skyzoom00@gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Project</title>
      <link>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shapetheworld.netlify.com/about/</guid>
      <description>February 2, 2018
 Let’s pretend that it’s 2050, and life is better than anyone ever imagined. We can&#39;t believe how people use to live in 2018! How barbaric! You&#39;re credited in the history books as being central to humanity&#39;s success.  What did you do to make 2050 so remarkable? Guidelines

No, there is not a word count. Write enough so that you can explain your idea fully, but not so that it’s a full on dissertation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>